Long ago, there existed
a brilliant young scientist.
By dint of his astonishing genius,
he was able to make a number of
contributions to human knowledge.
However, eventually he became
disillusioned with the world.
Though constantly showered with
praise for the subtlety of his mind,
none of his ideas or
theories ever received
even the slightest support
from the scientific community.
"We should not be striving
to advance human civilization,
but rather the artificial
evolution of humans as a species."
That was the only dream he ever had.
But not a single person came forward
to help him fulfill that dream.
Damn these apes!
"Dangerous ideas?"
Writing about me as if I were some freak?
Do they really think humans have come
this far by avoiding risks?
Idiots who think
they no longer need to evolve
have no right to pass on their genes!
Of course, this plan was always
for my own sake.
I will carry it out...
even if I must do it all myself!
Thereafter, he devoted himself to research.
It was only after he turned 70
that his efforts began to yield results.
First, the scientist regained his youth.
Next, he began cloning himself.
He named his laboratory
the "House of Evolution"
and together with his clones
he conducted countless experiments
with animals to create new species.
Eventually, his experiments shifted to
human subjects—
This is taking too long!
...eh?
What's this got to do with me?
You're just trying to act cool again.
Just get to the point, okay?
My master is a busy man.
Summarize it in 20 words or less.
...I-I'm sorry.
One punch
Three, two, one, kill shot
sanjou, hisshou, shijou saikyou
He joins the fight, he wins, the strongest in history
nan datten da, frustration
Are you talking to him? Frustration ☹
ore wa tomaranai
He's not going to stop
one punch, kanryou, rensenrenshou
One punch, that's it, one fight after another
ore wa katsu, tsune ni katsu, asshou
He wins, he always wins, overwhelmingly
power, get power
Power, get power
girigiri genkai made
On to the very edge
Hero
ore o tataeru koe ya
There are voices praising him
kassai nante hoshiku wa nai sa
but he's not doing this for acclaim
Hero
dakara hitoshirezu aku to tatakau
So he just fight evil without end
Nobody knows who he is
sora ooi oshiyoseru teki
Enemies to fight are numerous as the stars
ore wa se wo muke wa shinai
and he's not gonna turn his back on you
Hero
naraba yuruginaki kakugo shita tame
He's made up his mind and ain't gonna yield
tatakau hero
A fighting hero
kodoku na hero
A lone hero
I
i wanna be a saikyou hero
I wanna be the strongest hero
So, in other words, my boss has become
very curious about your body.
I'm not interested in dudes.
I think you misunderstood, Master.
He plans to use your body,
which surpasses normal human limitations,
for his research on evolution.
If we don't do something,
I'm sure he'll try again.
We cannot allow him a free hand.
Our move should be to attack him.
Sure, let's go.
Okay.
Huh?
Now?!
Yeah, there's a sale on tomorrow.
Can't do it then.
Master!
This doesn't sound good.
Better tell the Doctor...
Hey, you.
Oh. Yes?
I have one last question.
Was the "House of Evolution" developing
cyborgs prior to four years ago?
How many more cyborgs are there?
Have any of them destroyed towns
in the past?
I'm not sure,
but at the "House of Evolution,"
I'm the only combat cyborg.
Impossible!
Our elite force, formed for the extermination
of these obsolete humans, wiped out?!
According to Armored Gorilla's report,
the two responsible are on their way here.
If they come,
all our research, everything we've been
working on, could be destroyed.
This is a serious matter.
The only option is to use our trump card.
Begin preparations for the release of
Asura Kabuto.
What?!
-No, not him!
-That's crazy!
-He'll finally be released?
-He's right. That might be the only way.
-But maybe we should stop him.
-It's too dangerous.
-I have a bad feeling about this.
-Is that the only way?
Be calm!
He will be our last resort.
But...
First, from the first to the eighth floor,
we'll activate all our traps.
If we're lucky, they will take care of
the intruders.
I'm fully aware of what will happen to me
should we fail.
I didn't think we'd be running
the whole way.
How else are we gonna get there?
I was sure you could fly or something.
Humans can't fly, you know.
It's amazing that you are never late.
As expected from a hero.
Nah, I hardly ever arrive on time.
We're here.
This is the place Gorilla told us of.
So this is...
...the "House of Evolution."
One, two, three, four, five, six...
Looks like it's about eight stories high—
Uh...what was that all of a sudden?
Yes. I decided it would be most efficient
to destroy them all in one swoop.
Well, that's true but...
We could have at least seen
what the bad guys had in store for us.
That was kind of mean.
Looks like there's a basement.
S-Stop!!
Hey, Asura Kabuto.
Are you well?
It appears you've killed
a bunch of my clones again.
Satisfied?
Huh?
Fool!
Do I look like I'm satisfied?
I've been kept locked up
deep beneath the Earth.
I, the strongest warrior in the entire
"House of Evolution."
You are mentally unstable. We couldn't
control you. There was no choice.
Control me?
You idiot!
I am the culmination of the "New Human"
you guys have sought for so long.
My intelligence and physical strength
and your own are incomparable!
You should be the ones obeying me.
No. You're a failure.
It's true you perform
at unheard of levels,
but it is humanity you lack.
Go ahead, kill me.
Plenty of clones could take my place.
Oh?
But I have a favor to ask first.
There's a specimen I must have.
He is extremely strong.
Only you can defeat him.
I want you to catch him for me...
...dead or alive.
This basement is huge!
I'm getting kind of fired up.
Huh?
I sense living beings deeper in...
Master, two of them are approaching.
Oh, here I come!
There are two. Which one is it?
The one on the right...
In that case, you don't need the one
on the left!
Genos?
Huh?
Hey...
I am Asura Kabuto!
We got a combat experimentation room.
Let's do this in there.
You turned Genos into a piece of
modern art.
Fight's on!
Pretty big, eh?
It's the biggest room in the facility.
This is where they make us fight
to test our combat abilities.
Well then, let's start the killing—
Oh?
Still alive, huh?
You fool!
Machinegun Blows!
He got me.
Let me...
...take him...
Your face is all cracked.
Don't push yourself.
With his breath? Impossible!
Genos, you okay?
Yes...
But, your head doesn't look alright!
You've gone and gotten my hopes up.
I have always been critical of humans
and their inferior abilities.
The entire species, aside from myself,
can be viewed only as dumb animals.
That realization was agony for me.
If memory serves right, I was 15
when it occurred to me.
A plan to evolve
the human animal
and create a world
where I could live contentedly.
A utopia of my own, created by me.
A world made up of only us,
the new human breed
that will transcend humanity!
I must see it through.
Compared to my anguish back then,
this physical pain I feel now is nothing.
What's the hold up? Let's go!
Bring everything you've got.
Asura Kabuto—a demon incarnate,
the strongest and most brutal
creation of the House of Evolution.
Let's see how you, at your archaic
stage of human development,
fare against a monster that is
the final form of artificial evolution.
Or will you be the trigger for
a new evolution?
I can't wait to find out!
Oh, I see it. I see it!
You're supposed to be strong.
Don't disappoint me now.
You're this place's ultimate weapon, right?
You're clearly not the same as the guys
from this morning.
Look at you, just oozing with confidence.
He's fast!
What are you doing?
Hey.
He just backed off?
Asura Kabuto?!
If I'd attacked him just now,
he'd have killed me.
Who the hell is this guy?
He's leaving himself wide open,
yet all my instincts are screaming,
sending out danger signals!
Huh?
You bastard!
Just how in the
world did you get that strong?
So you wanna know too?
Okay, fine.
Genos, you listen carefully too.
He's going to tell us right now?
The secret to Master's power...?
I'd like to know too.
Huh?
Who are you?
I am Genus.
Well, fine. Listen up.
It's too risky! He can't let
these guys know his secret!
First, what's important is, to make sure
you stick to this intense training regimen.
Training? Not modification surgery
or genetic enhancement,
but training?
What training...?
Listen, Genos.
You just have to keep doing it.
No matter how hard it gets.
It took me three years to get this strong.
One hundred push-ups!
One hundred sit-ups!
One hundred squats!
Then a ten kilometer run.
Every single day!
And of course, make sure you eat
three meals a day.
Just a banana in the morning is fine.
But the most important thing is
Save Money
to never use the A/C or heat
in the summer or winter
so that you can strengthen the mind.
In the beginning, you'll wish
you were dead.
You might start thinking
what's the harm of taking a day off?
But for me, in order to be a strong hero,
no matter how tough it was,
even if I was spitting blood,
I never stopped.
I kept doing squats even when my legs
were so heavy they refused to move.
Even when my arms started making
weird clicking noises,
I kept doing push-ups.
A year and a half later, I started
to notice a difference.
I was bald...
And I had become stronger!
In other words, you gotta train like hell
to the point where your hair falls out.
That's the only way to become strong.
The guys that are fooling around with
the "new human race" and evolution junk
will never make it this far.
Human beings are strong because
we have the ability to change ourselves.
W-What?
Is this guy...for real?
Master...
You are so...
FULL OF CRAP!
Huh?
That is nothing but
standard strength training!
And it's not even that intense!
It's just a normal level!
I...I have to get stronger. I didn't ask
to study under you just to hear jokes!
Master Saitama,
your power is clearly stronger than
what you'd get from just training your body.
That's right, I want to know your—
We want to know your true secret!
Genos...
You may not believe me,
but that's really all I did.
Oh yeah?
No! Asura Kabuto!
If you don't wanna tell us your secret...
so be it.
Stop! You'll go on another rampage!
I bet you aren't stronger than me anyway!
But, since you pissed me off,
I'm gonna annihilate you.
ASURA
MODE
Asura Mode!
When I get like this I lose control
for a whole week
and my lust for death cannot be quelled!
After I kill you, I'll head into town and go on
a killing rampage until next Saturday!
If you are indeed a strong hero,
then try and stop me!
No way... it can't be.
Master?!
Dammit.
I might have made
a horrible mistake.
This guy's in Asura mode...
He said he'll be on a rampage
for a whole week?
Death, death, death, death, death, death,
Death, death, death, death, death!!
He'll be like this till next Saturday?
One whole week from today...
Next Saturday...
In other words, today
is Saturday too.
That means...
It's all over.
There's no one in this world
that can stop him.
That means...
Today is...
Bargain day at the supermarket!!
Who the hell is this guy?
I screwed up!!!
What is he—
I'm pretty sure he's upset about this.
Master, the store closes at 10:00 PM.
That is about four hours away.
If we really hurry, we can make it.
I'll make it if I hurry?
Yes!
Let's go, Genos!
Yes, Master!
I think I'm done...
...with evolution.
It appears that...
...I am the one who must change.
Hey, come back home soon
On nights when the new moon shivers from my sighs
I close my eyes and think of you
I want to see you... I feel like crying
I feel so romantic
I hope these feelings reach you
I know very well
how hard you work all the time
You're the one I love
You're so strong but I'm still worried
Don't hide your weakness, at least show it to me
I'll find you before any stars
Come straight back home
Hey, come back home soon
Yes. The on-site investigation
is underway.
Yes, that's correct.
Just like the other cases, the area has been
thoroughly burnt by intense flames.
Everything points to the young cyborg
being responsible for this.
Yes, understood.
Such a devastating amount of power.
Yeah...
NEXT
EPISODE
THE MODERN NINJA
Yo, this is Asura Kabuto.
In Japanese my name is "Ashura Kabuto,"
and the kanji come from "Shell," "Field Trip"
and the sanskrit word "Aum."
Whaddaya think?
Bah, you don't give a damn!
Coming next on One-Punch Man is
episode 4, "The Modern Ninja."
So that guy is finally gonna show up?